翻译：@隐秀_（seriouszyx）
The last thing we're going to change about our ArrayList is to make it generic.
我们要改变 ArrayList 的最后一件事是使它成为泛型
Now there wouldn't be anything to do,
现在没什么可做的了
I wouldn't even make this video if it weren't for one little syntactical quirk of Java.
如果不是因为 Java 语法的小怪癖，我甚至不会做这个视频
So let's see it pop up.
来看代码
So I need to, in order to make my ArrayList generic, I, of course, need to pick a type parameter name.
为了使 ArrayList 成为泛型，我需要选择一个参数类型的名称
I could pick Blorp or whatever, but I'm going to pick item, which is a little more common.
我可以选择 Blorp 什么的，但倾向于更常见的 Item
Now there's nothing special about putting item here.
把 Item 放在这没什么特别
It's not a special keyword in Java.
它不是 Java 特殊的关键字
It just happens to be the one I'm going to use.
恰好是我要用的
Now I'm going to go through and I'm going to say instead of it being an int array, it's going to be an item array.
再说一遍，它不是一个整型数组，而是一个 Item 数组
AList, instead of being a new int array,
AList 不再是整型数组
it will say new item, 100 let's say.
而是 Item，比方说100
As we move our way forward, when we resize
前进道路上，当 resize 时...
what else do we need to do?
还需要做什么呢？
This should be an item array.
这应该是 Item 数组
Continuing to move forward, everything here looks good, except addLast needs to take item.
继续往前，一切很好，addLast 需要 Item
getLast returns an item, get returns an item,
getLast 返回 Item，get 返回 Item
and removeLast will return an item as well.
removeLast 也将返回 Item
So we'll notice there's actually a couple of syntax errors.
我们会注意到有几个语法错误
And we see that Java is complaining.
Java 在抱怨
In fact, if we hover over, we see item cannot be instantiated directly.
将鼠标悬停在上面，我们会看到 Item 不能直接实例化
Item cannot be instantiated directly.
Item 不能直接实例化
Required item found A. OK, well that one we can change.
需要 Item 发现 a，换掉
So what does this mean?
这意味着什么？
Item cannot be instantiated directly.
Item 不能直接实例化
There's an annoying feature of Java,
Java 有一个恼人的特性
which is that generic arrays are not allowed.
不允许使用泛型数组
You simply cannot do them.
你根本不能这样做
So instead, you have to do--
取而代之，你需要...
and just trust me for now--
现在请相信我...
this very strange thing.
这很奇怪
Instead of saying new item, we say new object.
不能 new Item，而是 new Object
Now when we do new object, it now says, required item, but found object.
new Object 时，它会显示“需要 Item，但发现 Object”
No problem.
没问题
I'll instead do this other mysterious thing, where I'm going to type the word item here, put the braces, and now things will work.
我会做另一件神秘的事情，在这里输入 Item[]，现在就可以了
This is a cast.
这是转换
We'll learn about casts later.
稍后会学到
But for now that's just what we need to know.
这目前正是我们需要的
This is just a side effect of the strange way that generics were created in Java.
这只是 Java 中创建泛型奇怪方式的一个副作用
And so effectively what it boils down to is instead of saying new item yada yada.
归根结底，就是不能 new Item 什么的
In Java, we have to do parentheses, item, braces, space, new object.
Java 中必须 (Item[]) new Object
And that's only because Java specifically does not allow you to create arrays of generic objects.
这只是因为 Java 明确不允许创建泛型对象的数组
So at this point our code should compile,
现在代码可以编译了
except that we should have made this into an item as well.
应该把这个改成 Item
So now we see everything.
全都看看
We see no compilation errors.
没有编译错误
And in the real world again, we'd test, but not in this lecture.
现实中会进行测试，但课上就不了
And so we end up with a nice ArrayList.
最终得到了一个很好的 ArrayList
So this on the left is our ArrayList code that holds only integers.
左边的 ArrayList 代码只保存整型
And this right here is our ArrayList that holds arbitrary things.
右边的包含任何东西
I used Glorp on the slides.
我在幻灯片用了 Glorp
Or used items before.
Item 也行
And the only really interesting thing is this.
唯一有趣的是这个
There's one more interesting detail, which is that--
还有一个有趣的细节
well, actually maybe I should summarize real quick.
实际上也许我应该快速总结一下
So in a sense, our issue is that when we create an array of references to Glorps or items or whatever,
在某种意义上，问题是，当我们创建一个 Glorp 或 Item 之类的数组时
instead of saying new Glorp, we say Glorp, braces, new object, however many items.
不能 new Glorp，而是 (Glorp[]) new object[cap]
This will, by the way if you use the command line compilation,
顺便说一下，如果使用命令行编译
it will give you a compiler warning.
会有一个编译器警告
And if that happens, you've just gotta ignore it.
如果发生，你只能忽略它
It's the thing we have to deal with, because of the funny way that Java was created.
这是必须处理的事情，因为 Java 的创建方式很有趣
If you did actually do new Glorp,
如果你真的 new Glorp
you will get if you use the command line compilation,
使用命令行编译将得到
generic array creation error.
泛型数组创建错误
And we'll talk about these funny language issues later.
以后会讨论这些有趣的语言问题
But for now, they're just not that interesting.
目前而言，它们并不那么有趣
I want to focus on the interesting stuff.
要关注有趣的东西
And we'll deal java minutia in the future.
我们将在未来处理 Java 细节
Now there's one other thing we do want to change about our code that's a little more subtle.
我们确实要改变代码的话，还有一件更不容易察觉的事
So what we had before will work correctly.
之前拥有的将会正常工作
But it does something called loitering, which I don't like.
但它做的一些事称为“闲逛”，我不喜欢
So unlike integer-based ALists, remember whenever we're doing the allegory of the cave,
不同于基于整型的 AList，回想我们洞穴的寓言故事
we did not actually destroy the bird that someone finger shot.
实际上并没有摧毁用手指射杀的那只鸟
We didn't actually overwrite things with zeros.
实际上并没有用0重写
Now actually we do want to overwrite things.
我们确实想重写一些东西
So the difference is we are actually going to say items size minus 1 equals null.
不同之处是 items[size - 1] = null
Let's just get that down.
把它记下
So after we get the last item, we will say item size minus 1 equals null.
在获得最后一项后，items[size - 1] = null
So why are we shooting the bird here?
为什么要在这里射鸟呢？
What's going on?
到底怎么回事？
Well the issue is imagine here we have an array that happens to hold pictures of loitering signs.
想象一下，我们这里有一个数组保存闲逛标志的图片
So in position zero, we have this one.
位置0有这个
In position one we have this one.
位置1有这个
In position two we have this one.
位置2有这个
So remember that Java only destroys unwanted objects,
记住 Java 只销毁不需要的对象
only does garbage collections when the last reference has been lost.
最后一个引用丢失时才执行垃圾回收
If you keep a bunch of references around to unneeded objects, then that object will persist somewhere in memory.
如果保留大量不需要的对象的引用，那么该对象将持久保存在内存中的某个位置
So this image could actually be maybe a megabyte in size.
这张图片实际上可能有一兆字节
And because you're keeping the address stored of this object,
因为你保存的是这个对象的地址
Java will never delete it.
Java 永远不会删除它
So this is considered loitering.
这被认为是闲逛
And so by setting this thing to null
通过将该值设置为 null
what will happen if we say size equal-- sorry--
如果我们说 size 等于...抱歉
if we don't set this to null, when we reduce size to 2, then there's still a link.
如果不将其设置为 null，当 size 减少到2时，仍然有一个链接
Look at that. It's horrible.
看啊，太可怕了
And so basically we're wasting all this memory storing a reference to the sign image,
基本上我们是在浪费内存来存储标志图像的引用
and we just have this Getty Images thing laying around.
这张图片就静静躺在那
By contrast, if we null all this out,
相反，如果清空了
then that garbage collector would come around and say, you know what.
垃圾回收器就会过来
Nobody actually cares about this image anymore.
已经没人在关心这张图片了
I may as well destroy it.
还不如把它毁了
So it's a very subtle point you might never notice unless you're storing objects,
这是很不容易察觉的点，除非你在存储对象
storing an array of really large objects.
存储非常大的对象数组
But we do need to do this when we're using generics,
使用泛型时确实需要这么做
otherwise we're loitering.
否则就是在闲逛
So don't loiter.
不要闲逛
And you might really go back to earlier and think,
回到早些时候想想
what was special about objects versus just integers.
与整数相比，对象的特殊之处在于
Make sure this really makes sense.
确保这真的有意义
翻译：@隐秀_（seriouszyx）
Because it's a subtle point, but an important one.
这点不易察觉，但非常重要